<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <jokeList>
    <Joke>
      <sJoke>A man walks up to the pub and is about to go into it when the nun starts shouting. &quot;BEFORE YOU ENTER THIS DEN OF SIN, THINK OF YOUR MOTHER AND YOUR FATHER!&quot;
He said back to the nun. &quot;They&apos;re dead, they&apos;re dead and in heaven&quot;
The nun went for a different tack and said. &quot;Think then! Think of the damage the alcohol will do to your brain!&quot;
&quot;What? Whatever are ye talking about? Have you ever had a drink?&quot;
And the nun said no.
&quot;Well how the hell can you stand there and talk about the damage the alcohol is gonna do to your brain if ye never had it? I tell ye what, I&apos;ll go in there, buy ye a drink, take it out here, you can try it and if you don&apos;t like THEN ye can talk about it. But don&apos;t talk about things ye&apos;ve never experienced. What will ye have?&quot;
And the nun says. &quot;I don&apos;t know, what do ladies drink?&quot;
&quot;Gin&quot;
and she says &quot;Alright I&apos;ll have a gin. But get it in a cup so nobody will notice.&quot;
The fella goes into the bar and says to the barman &quot;Get us a pint of beer and a double gin in a cup.&quot;
The barman replies &quot;Ah fer christ&apos;s sake is that bloody nun out there again?&quot;</sJoke>
      <sPunchline></sPunchline>
      <iCategoryID>0</iCategoryID>
    </Joke>
    <Joke>
      <sJoke>A father buys a lie detector robot that slaps people when they lie.

He decides to test it out at dinner one night. The father asks his son what he did that afternoon.

The son says, &quot;I did some schoolwork.&quot;

The robot slaps the son.

The son says, &quot;Ok, Ok. I was at a friend&apos;s house watching movies.&quot;

Dad asks, &quot;What movie did you watch?&quot;

Son says, &quot;Toy Story.&quot;

The robot slaps the son.

Son says, &quot;Ok, Ok, we were watching porn.&quot;

Dad says, &quot;What? At your age I didn&apos;t even know what porn was.&quot;

The robot slaps the father.

Mom laughs and says, &quot;Well, he certainly is your son.&quot;

The robot slaps the mother.

Robot for sale.</sJoke>
      <sPunchline></sPunchline>
      <iCategoryID>0</iCategoryID>
    </Joke>
  </jokeList>